维多利亚的秘密 时尚内衣秀
(时间轴纠正&再制作：句点 QQ624940523）
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
彩色蜡笔
吝啬
傅莉迪
夏沫
断电
子衿
Remember
瓜瓜
校对&监制：馒头的Ellen姨生日快乐
舞者上场
Sending the dancers out.
? Angels lift you off the ground ?
典雅芭蕾
将由Candice开场
We're gonna start with you on Candice.
准备就绪
We are ready.
收到
Copy that.
候场  音效如何  10秒倒计时吗
Stand by. How's sound? Ten counts?
-天使们还在换装中  -享受起来
- They're still getting into costume. - Suck it in.
该上场了
We got to go.
我们上
Let's go.
? You believe in me ?
维多利亚的秘密时尚内衣秀
This is the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show
10秒后开场
in ten seconds.
来场盛宴吧
Let's do it.
-震翻全场  -翅膀来了
- Bring it on. - Wings coming!
感觉我心跳加速
My heart's beating quite fast.
我怎么会不紧张呢
How can I not be nervous?
-准备好了吗  -完全就绪
- Are you ready?  - Totally ready.
有人看到Erin了吗
Anybody got eyes on Erin?
开场了  开场了  开场了
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes.
Candice  104音轨
Candice at 104.
好戏开演
Showtime.
? Take me, I'm alive ?
? Never was a girl with a wicked mind ?
? But everything looks better when the sun goes down ?
Lily  走起
Go, Lily.
? I had everything ?
? Opportunities for eternity ?
? And I could belong to the night ?
? Your eyes, your eyes ?
? I can see in your eyes ?
? Your eyes ?
? You make me wanna die ?
? I'll never be good enough ?
? And everything you love will burn up in the light ?
脱掉  脱掉
Get it off! Get it off!
拿掉首饰
Get the jewelry off!
? Look inside your eyes ?
? Make me wanna die ?
Doutzen上台
Go, Doutzen!
来了  来了
Coming in! Coming in!
? Taste me, drink my soul ?
? Show me all the things that I shouldn't know ?
? And there's a new moon on the rise ?
? I had everything ?
? Opportunities for eternity ?
? And I could belong to the night ?
? Your eyes, your eyes ?
? I can see in your eyes, your eyes ?
? Everything in your eyes, your eyes ?
Lais  准备好了吗
Are you eady, Lais?
? You make me wanna die ?
? I'll never be good enough ?
上  Lais
Go, Lais!
? Everything you love will burn up in the light ?
? And every time I look inside your eyes ?
? Burning in the light ?
? Make me wanna die ?
上
Go!
? I'll die for you, my love ?
? My love ?
? I'll lie for you, my love ?
? Make me wanna die ?
? And I'll steal for you, my love ?
? My love ?
? Make me wanna die ?
? I'll die for you, my love ?
? My love ?
? We'll burn up in the light ?
? And every time I look inside your eyes ?
? I'm burning in the light ?
? Look inside your eyes ?
? I look inside your eyes ?
? You make me wanna die ?
哦哦  鞋子要掉了
Oh, oh, oh. Shoe is gone.
松掉的鞋子下场   镜头右移
Broken shoe coming, camera right.
Kanye准备
Stand by, Kanye.
紧张吗
Are you nervous?
不
Nah.
走上维多利亚的秘密时尚秀舞台
I think it's every girl's dream to walk in
是所有女孩的梦想
the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show.
每个人都明白这场秀的意义
Everybody knows what a big deal it is.
首次走秀时
You kind of feel like
你会有点懵懂迷茫
a deer in headlights your first show.
我的维密处女秀
My first Victoria's Secret Fashion Show
是在2000年
was the year 2000.
身边名模环绕
I was definitely very nervous about
让我紧张万分
all the models I was gonna be next to.
? What do I have to do ?
只在图片或电视上见过的天使们
It was so amazing to see
真正出现在面前  真是不可思议
the Angels that I'd only seen in pictures or on TV.
有Heidi Klum
Heidi Klum was there,
还有Tyra Banks
Tyra Banks was there.
我站在一边静静地看着
I stood back and watched
Alessandra和Adriana
Alessandra and Adriana
不住地惊叹
like... wow.
我来这干嘛呀
What am I doing here?
真是难以想象
Like, this is crazy.
? You're a million miles ?
? A million miles away ?
在后台整装待发时
Standing backstage in my outfit ready to go out,
我紧张极了
I was so nervous.
但一踏上天桥
But the minute I stood on the runway,
立刻镇定  风情油然而生
I feel like I became a woman.
我当时想  天呐  太赞了
I was like, oh, my God, it's so amazing!
内心激荡
It was overwhelming.
那种感觉  一生都难以忘怀
It's something that will stick with you forever.
当年我初为天使
I was an Angel then.
感觉真是无与伦比
And I just felt fabulous.
我现在又来啦
And here I am now.
时刻准备走下一场秀
Ready for another one.
试镜
新天使们总能为维密带来
New girls always bring a vitality and an energy
生气  活力  刺激以及紧张感
and excitement and a nervousness to the show
维密工作人员
这点很好
that is great.
她讨人喜欢
She's adorable.
没错  我很喜欢
Yes. I love her.
我们找到了一位美丽佳人
We really found a beautiful girl.
堪称完美
She is perfection.
我们告诉她  她将参与维密秀
We told her that she was gonna be in the show.
这消息让她无比激动
Which she was so excited about.
维密工作人员
我在圣路易斯长大
Growing up in St. Louis
是个地道美国女孩
and being an American girl,
这一天居然来了  我要飞啦
This is it. I'm getting my wings!
像是美国梦成真了
I really feel like I'm living the American dream.
开秀当天
快来  要迟到啦
All right, hurry up, we're late. Come on.
? Happiness hit her ?
传说中的粉红袍
This is the famous pink robe.
快成为维密秀的标志了
It's becoming official.
居然这就开始了
I can't believe it's already time.
-第一次上维密  Karlie加油  -紧张死了
- It's her first show! Go, Karlie! Go, Karlie! - I'll die...
? The dog days are over ?
居然要开秀了
I can't believe it's almost showtime.
超级紧张的
I'm freaking out.
? The dog days are over ?
? The dog days... ?
-上场啦  -走  走  走
- Let's rock! - Go, go, go!
麻烦帮我喷点发胶
I need some hair spray, guys.
Lindsay  把人带来换衣服
Lindsay-- lift her up and let's get wardrobe here now.
-请回答  -老天
- Give me an update, please. - Oh, my goodness.
我要发胶
Hair spray!
Kanye West准备上台
Going into Kanye West next.
-谁有发胶  -各位准备好
- Does anybody have hair spray? - All right, stand by, guys.
女士们先生们  有请Kanye West
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome Mr. Kanye West.
2007年  我本准备在维密演唱这首歌
In 2007, I was supposed to perform this song on this show.
我的超级英雄  我的母亲  却在那年去世
And I lost my super hero.
现在她是我的天使  我的力量之源
Now she's my super angel.
? Work it harder, make it better ?
? Do it faster, makes us stronger ?
? More than ever, ever after ?
? Our work is never over ?
? Work it harder, make it better ?
? Do it faster, makes us stronger ?
? More than ever, ever after ?
? Our work is never over ?
? Let's get lost tonight ?
? You could be my black Kate Moss tonight ?
? Play secretary, I'm the boss tonight ?
? And you don't give a fuck what they all say, right? ?
? Awesome, the Christian and Christian Dior ?
? Damn, they don't make 'em like this anymore ?
Shannon上
Go, Shannon!
? I ask 'cause I'm not sure ?
? Do anybody make real hits anymore? ?
? Bow in the presence of greatness ?
? 'Cause right now thou has forsaken us ?
? You should be honored by my lateness ?
? That I would even show up to this fake ... ?
? So go ahead, go nuts, go ape ?
? Especially in my pastel on my bape ?
? Act like you can't tell who made this ?
? New gospel, homey, take six, and take this, haters ?
? Now that don't kill me can only make me stronger ?
? I need you to hurry up now ?
? 'Cause I can't wait much longer ?
Karlie上
Go, Karlie.
? I know I got to be right now ?
? 'Cause I can't get much wronger ?
? Man, I've been waiting all night now ?
? That's how long I've been on you ?
? Work it harder, make it better ?
? I need you right now, now ?
? Oh, I need you right now ?
? I don't know if you got a man or not ?
? If you made plans or not ?
? And God put me in your plans or not ?
? I'm tripping, this drink got me saying a lot ?
? But I know that God put you in front of me ?
Karlie上
Go, Karlie.
? So how the hell could you front on me? ?
? There's a thousand yous, there's only one of me ?
? I'm tripping, I'm caught up in this moment, right? ?
? This is Louis Vuitton Don night ?
? So we gonna do everything that Kan like ?
? Heard they'd do anything for a Klondike ?
? Well, I'd do anything for a blonde night ?
Behati上
Go, Behati.
? And she'll do anything for the limelight ?
? And we'll do anything when the time's right ?
? Uh, baby, you're making it ?
? Harder, better, faster, stronger ?
? Baby, you're making it! ?
真不敢相信
I can't believe it!
太棒了  我是维密天使耶
It's nice. I'm an Angel!
? I need you to hurry up now ?
? 'Cause I can't wait much longer ?
? I know I got to be right now ?
? 'Cause I can't get much wronger ?
? Man, I've been waiting all night now ?
再来一次
One last time
? That's how long I've been on you ?
把手举起来
Throw your hands up!
手举高
Hands up high!
? Oh, I need you right now ?
? You know how long I been on you? ?
? Since Prince was on Apollonia ?
? Since OJ had Isotoners ?
? Don't act like I never told you ?
? Oh, don't act like I never told you ?
? Uh! Baby, you're making it ?
? Harder, better, faster, stronger ?
? Baby, you're making it ?
? Now that that don't kill me can only make me stronger ?
? I need you to hurry up now ?
? 'Cause I can't get much wronger ?
? I know I got to be right now ?
? Man, I've been waiting all night now ?
? That's how long I been on you ?
如果我是超级英雄
If I was a superhero...
老天  这词儿好熟
Ooh, oh, my God, I know this one.
如果我有超能力
If I was a superhero and I had a superpower
我想飞起来
I would love to be able to fly.
我想时间旅行[穿越天使]
I would be able to time-travel.
吱吱  就移形换影啦
Zzt! And we would be, like, totally somewhere else.
读心吧
Maybe mind reading.
我要看出别人在想什么
I would love to be able to read what everybody's thinking...
肯定很好玩
Which I think would be really funny,
但乐了两分钟后
but probably only fun for, like two minutes,
估计我就要喊停了
and then I'd be, like, "Turn it off!"
如果能有超能力  我想隐形
If I had a superpower, I would love to be invisible.
偷偷四处潜伏
'Cause then you can kind of like sneak around,
偷窥别人啦
see what happens, you know?
顺便拳脚报复
And kick some ass.
各位  Maroon 5候场
Okay, guys, Maroon 5 are on the move.
Kanye准备好  Jay-Z已到场
Kanye is clear and Jay-Z is in the building.
重复  Jay-Z已到场
I repeat, Jay-Z is in the building.
Nicki Minaj正走向后台
We have Nicki. She's on her way to you now.
热恋风情
本环节要重点突出
The idea for us for the "Passion" was to have this
本系列创意总监
高端时尚感
couturey hand to it.
本系列主题元素是
It was built on the idea of, like,
本系列设计师
性感的拉丁  西班牙风情
seductive Latin, Spanish references.
这一件由Canvas设计
This piece by Canvas,
大概是整场秀最昂贵的作品了
it's probably one of the most expensive pieces in the show.
是在印度纯手工刺绣的
It's all hand-embroidered in India.
还有黑玉串珠镶边
It's got jet beading.
非常奢华的设计
That's a really opulent outfit.
这一套扇状羽翼镶金串珠
This fan wing that's sort of gold-plated and bejeweled
仿造西班牙骨扇形状
is meant to represent a Spanish fan
做成了翅膀
which we've made into a wing.
这套内衣很美  镶了很多水晶
The lingerie's really beautiful. It has lots of crystals.
我全身亮晶晶
My body is, like, full of crystals,
还有这华丽的翅膀
and I have this back piece, you know, like my wings.
真是太美了
It's just amazing.
"热恋风情"准备上场  摄像换景
Stand by, "Passion." Camera left.
Alessandra准备
Standing by, Alessandra.
三  二  一  上台
Three, two, one. Go!
? Chest to chest ?
? Nose to nose ?
? Palm to palm ?
? We were always just that close ?
? Wrist to wrist ?
? Toe to toe ?
? Lips that felt just like the inside of a rose ?
? So how come when I reach out my finger ?
? It feels like more than distance between us ?
? In this California king bed ?
? We're 10,000 miles apart ?
? I've been California wishing on these stars ?
快点  换快点  她要上场了
Move it. Change her fast. She's walking in this runway.
? My California king ?
? Eye to eye ?
快点  要来不及了
Hurry, she's gonna miss her walk, guys.
-再不上就来不及了  -马上让Adriana过来
- She's gonna miss her walk. - Need Adriana now.
? You were sleeping next to me ?
? Arm in arm ?
? Dusk to dawn ?
? With the curtains drawn ?
? And a little last night on these sheets ?
? So how come when I reach out my fingers ?
? It seems like more than distance between us ?
? In this California king bed ?
? We're 10,000 miles apart ?
? I've been California wishing on these stars ?
? For your heart on me, my California king ?
Adriana在我这儿  准备好了
I got Adriana, stage right.
? You turned around and gave me one last touch ?
上啊  让她上就行  已经叫到她了
Just send her! Send her! She's already been cued.
? And even then, my eyes got wetter ?
? So confused, wanna ask you if you love me ?
? But I don't want to seem so weak ?
? Maybe I've been California dreaming ?
? Hey, hey, hey, hey ?
? In this California king bed ?
? We're 10,000 miles apart ?
? I've been California wishing on these stars ?
? For your heart on me, my California king. ?
真美
Lovely.
-天呐  -我的天
- Oh, my gosh. - Oh, my God.
看看我
Look at me.
你太可爱了
You look so cute.
小小体操选手  Behati
Little gymnast Behati.
实打实的倒挂金钩
Up to tricks, no doubt.
我穿了一双翅膀
I got these little wings on.
是学校的换装日
It was a dress-up day at school.
小时候有翅膀  现在也有呢
I had wings then and I've got wings now.
这是我俩的处女比基尼照
This is both our first bikini-shot moments.
非常不错嘛
I think we killed it.
好啦  来看这边的
Okay, let's talk about these now.
天呐
Oh, my gosh.
我有段很怂的时期  就是这张
I had a very awkward stage. And that was it.
我喜欢你这张
I love that picture of you.
好可爱哟
That's so cute.
这张很搞啊  这毛衣  看
This is hilarious, look at this sweater.
我妈妈很会打扮我们
My mom dressed us very interestingly.
各种可爱毛衣
A lot of sweaters.
我当时发型还很丑
And I always have this stupid haircut, too.
谢了  老妈
Thanks, Mom.
我的儿时梦想是当芭蕾舞者
When I was young, I wanted to be a ballerina,
后来想当医生
and then I wanted to be a doctor.
再后来想当宇航员
Then I wanted to be an astronaut.
我在非洲长大  梦想当个海洋生物学家
Growing up in Africa, I really wanted to be a marine biologist.
我小时候觉得
I thought I was going to be
长大会踢足球
a soccer player when I was little,
但读高中以后呢
but then when I got into high school,
就喜欢其他的东西了
I got more interested in other things, and...
喜欢男生了
Boys.
? Last Friday night, yeah, we danced on tabletops ?
感觉恍如隔世
It seems like another life,
-对  -看看这些照片
- Yeah. - These pictures.
我们都是小镇姑娘
We're like, both from a small town,
心里却有大大的梦想
and just like... Have big dreams.
好大的梦想
Yeah, we did have big dreams.
? Last Friday night ?
像每个小孩的梦一样
It's like a childhood dream, and...
小女孩们会看着我们  想
little girls are going to be looking at us, going,
"长大我也要做天使"
"Oh, one day I hope I'm an Angel."
她们肯定会的
I know. And they will be.
会有人变天使的  这场秀观众中会有的
Someone will be. Someone that's watching this will be an Angel.
? Skinny-dipping in the dark ?
现在回头看
Looking back on this,
我想说  你长大以后会是怎样
I would say that you should definitely not judge
现在说还太早
what you're going to be when you blossom by
现在你只是个孩子
what you are when you're a kid, because...
女大十八变嘛
a whole lot changes.
? This Friday night ?
乐队准备
Load the band.
上  现在上乐队
Go. Let's load the band now, please.
Maroon 5候场
Stand by for Maroon 5.
2010年维密时尚秀
去年我们在台下看秀
Last year, we were spectators. We were fans.
去年看热闹了  但今年
We were on the sidelines last year, but this year
Maroon 5主唱
[兼天使家属]
我们也参与了维密秀  很给力啊
we're actually a part of the show, which is really awesome.
这次能和他同台
Having him be on stage next to me is...
维密天使
这场秀肯定会非常美妙
I know we're going to have a... the best time ever.
我要上天桥咯
I'm going to be on a runway.
我也要上天桥咯
And I'm going to be on the runway, too.
身穿小胸罩和小内裤
Wearing a bra and panties.
Kanye  准备
Stand by, Kanye.
6号机拍Jay-Z  6号机拍Jay-Z
Six, Jay-Z. Jay-Z, six, Jay-Z.
请让Nicki就位
Can we get Nicki into position, please?
每一年  维密的服装
Every year, the Victoria's Secret outfits for the show
都越来越大  越来越美
get bigger and better.
完全猜不到设计师的下一步
You never know what they're going to do next.
宛如美妙的幻境
It's just like a beautiful fantasy.
一次美丽的逃离
You can get away with anything.
服装花了很大的功夫
There's so much work that goes into it.
各种精致的细节
So much attention to detail...
不知道他们每年怎么想出这些主题的
I don't know how they keep coming up with unique themes
这么多年了  每一年都各具特色
after all these years, but each year is so different.
从维密的第一场秀到现在
When you see the show from the first year till now,
设计师们越来越有创意
they get more creative, and they think of different things
不断创新  保持趣味活力
to keep it interesting and exciting.
小小的胸衣和底裤
It's amazing what they can do
在他们手中创意万千
with a bra and a pair of panties.
每一件服装
Each outfit, in itself,
都是一件艺术品
is a memorable piece.
我超爱我的拳击装
I love my boxing outfit,
很有力量感  很酷
because it's powerful. It's cool.
我喜欢那双蝴蝶的翅膀
I love the butterfly wings.
那是我第一年穿翅膀
And that was the first year I got to wear wings.
对我意义非凡
So that was really special.
我的最爱呢
My favorite ones that I wore
是圣诞装和糖果装
were the Christmas outfit, and the one with all the candy.
我超爱糖果的  所以
I love candy, so the outfit
服装闻起来超好吃
smelled delicious.
一整年来  设计师们
The designers spend the whole year
都在为这场秀找灵感
getting inspired to create the show.
他们创意不断  真的很奇妙
It's incredible, what goes through their head.
试衣
今天是试衣的日子
So I'm on my way to the fitting.
这是我生完小孩  回归的第一年
This is my first year back after having a baby,
超兴奋的
so it's super exciting.
等不及要看我的造型了
I can't wait to see what they have in store for me.
我们很激动
So we're really excited,
今天Miranda要来试衣
because today Miranda's coming in for her fitting.
她是"天使水世界"的开场模特
And she's opening the "Aquatic" Section.
维密工作人员
她将穿上
She's going to be wearing
价值250万美金的奢华胸衣
the $2 1/2 million fantasy bra this year.
背部是贝壳翅膀
and then it's framed by this big shell.
等不及要试试看了
Can't wait to put it on.
行啊  来吧
Yeah. Let's do it.
? You know I won't sleep tonight ?
? Oh, oh, I want some more ?
美死了  简直令人窒息
It's amazing. It really is just... breathtaking.
她真是美艳绝伦
She looks amazing.
我太爱这套设计了
I love it so much.
本系列创意总监
美啦
Good job.
我试好了行头  天桥上见啦
I've got my outfit. I'll see you on the runway.
女士们先生们  有请Maroon 5
Ladies and gentlemen, Maroon 5!
大家站起来
Get up!
天使水世界
? Just shoot for the stars ?
? If it feels right ?
? And aim for my heart ?
? If you feel like ?
? And take me away and make it okay ?
? I swear I'll behave ?
? You wanted control ?
? So we waited ?
? I put on a show, yeah, now I make it ?
? You say I'm a kid ?
? My ego is big ?
? I don't give a [shit] ?
? And it goes like this ?
? Take me by the tongue and I'll know you ?
? Kiss me till you're drunk, and I'll show you ?
? All the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves like jagger ?
? I don't need to try to control you, yeah ?
? Look into my eyes and I'll own you ?
? With the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves like jagger ?
? Baby it's hard ?
? When you feel like you're broken and scarred ?
? Nothing feels right ?
? But when you're with me ?
? I make you believe ?
? That I've got the key ?
? So get in the car ?
? We can ride it ?
? Wherever you want ?
? Get inside it ?
? And you want to steer ?
? But I'm shifting gears ?
? I'll take it from here ?
? And it goes like this ?
? Take me by the tongue and I'll know you ?
? Kiss me till you're drunk and I'll show you ?
? All the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves like jagger ?
? I don't need to try to control you ?
? Look into my eyes and I'll own you ?
? With the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves ?
? You want to know ?
? How to make me smile ?
? Take control, own me just for the night ?
? But if I share my secret ?
? Nobody else can see this ?
? So watch and learn ?
? I won't show you twice ?
? Head to toe, ooh baby, rub it right ?
? But if I share my secret ?
? You're gonna have to keep it ?
? Nobody else can see this, yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? And it goes like this ?
? Take me by the tongue and I'll know you ?
? Kiss me till you're drunk and I'll show you ?
? All the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves yeah ?
? Jagger, baby ?
? I don't need to try to control you ?
? Look into my eyes and I'll own you ?
? With the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves ?
? Like jagger, baby ?
? Take me by the tongue and I'll know you ?
? Kiss me till you're drunk and I'll show you ?
? All the moves like jagger ?
? 'Cause I got the moves like jagger ?
? Got the moves ?
? Like jagger ?
? Ooh, don't need to try to control you, yeah ?
? Look into my eyes and I'll own you ?
? With the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves like jagger ?
? I've got the moves ?
? Like jagger, baby ?
? Moves like jagger ?
这里是维密时尚内衣秀的后台
We're backstage at the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show,
Kanye West就离我几步远
and Kanye West is right there!
终于见到本尊啦
It's all happening.
Kanye  准备上场
Kanye, standing by.
Jay-Z  准备上场  谢谢
Stand by, Jay-Z. Thank you.
已经出来了
Stepping out now.
Nicki Minaj  准备就绪
We have Nicki Minaj, stage right and ready.
女士们先生们  有请Kanye West和Jay-Z
Ladies and gentlemen, Kanye West and Jay-Z.
我们唱且只唱这首歌
We're gonna skate to one song and one song only.
? Let's go ?
? Let's go, let's go ?
? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey ?
? Hova ?
? So I ball so hard, ... wanna fine me ?
? But first ... gotta find me ?
? What's 50 grand to a big baller like me ?
? Can you please remind me ?
? Ball so hard, this ... crazy ?
? Y'all don't know that don't ... phase me ?
? Nets could go 0-82 and I look at you like this ... gravy ?
? Ball so hard, this ... weird ?
? We ain't even s'pose to be here ?
? Ball so hard, since we here ?
? It's only right that we be fair ?
? Psycho, I'm liable to go Michael ?
? Take your pick, Jackson, Tyson, Jordan, game six ?
? Ball so hard, got a broke clock ?
? Rolleys that don't tick tock ?
? Audemars that's losing time ?
? Hidden behind all these big rocks ?
? Ball so hard, I'm shocked, too ?
? I'm supposed to be locked up, too ?
? If you escaped what we escaped ?
? You'd be in Paris getting ... up, too ?
? Ball so hard, that ... crazy ?
? Le Meurice for like six days ?
? Gold bottles, scold models, spillin' Ace on my sick J's ?
? Ball so hard, yeah, behave, just might let you meet Ye ?
? Chi Town, D Rose, I'm movin' the Nets ?
? Everybody bounce ?
? Ball so hard ... wanna fine me ?
? That ... crazy ?
? This ... crazy ?
? Ball so hard ... wanna fine me ?
? Yeah, that ... crazy, that ... crazy ?
? That ... crazy ? ? Know what she said? ?
? She said, "Ye, can we get married at the malal" ?
? I said, look, you need to crawl 'fore you ball ?
? Come and meet me in the bathroom stall ?
? And show me why you deserve to have it all ?
? Let's go! Ball so hard ?
? That is crazy, ain't it Jay? ?
? Ball so hard ?
? What she order, fish filet? ?
? Ball so hard ? ? Your whip so cold ?
? This old thing ? ? Ball so hard ?
? Act like you'll never be around ... like this again ?
? Bougie girl, grab her hand ?
? That girl, she don't wanna dance ?
? Excuse my French, but I'm in France ?
? I'm just sayin' ?
? Prince William's ain't do it right if you ask me ?
? 'Cause I was him, I would have married Kate & Ashley ?
? What's Gucci, my killa ?
? What's Louis, my killa ?
? What's drugs, my deala ?
? What's that jacket, Margiela ?
? Doctors say we the illest ?
? 'Cause we suffer from realness ?
? Got my homies in Paris ?
? And we going gorillas, huh ?
? I don't even know what that means ?
? No one knows what it means, but it's provocative ?
? - No, it's not... - Gets the people going ?
把手举起来
Hands up!
? You are now watching the throne ?
走吧  既然上了天桥  咱也走个秀
So, walk, let's walk it. We here, we might as well walk it.
拽
Swang!
我和天使们很熟
I know the Angels pretty well,
她们可不只有外表
and there's a lot more that meets the eye.
Adriana在台下
Adriana, off the runway,
是个疯狂的拳击手
is a crazy boxer.
? I'm on the edge of glory ?
给你看看我的关节
I show you my knuckles.
Adriana有了目标  就会奋斗
Adriana, she wants to do something, she'll do it.
她就像个女超人
She's like Super Woman.
没人能阻挡她
She's unstoppable.
? I'm on the edge with you ?
Candice很惹人疼爱
Candice is someone that you want to love,
但是她也有母老虎的一面
but then she has this tiger side.
她喜欢刺激
She's an adrenaline junky.
她爱玩滑翔伞
She loves hang-gliding.
她是冒险精神的化身
She totally embodies that essence of adventure
同时又是一个性感女神
and being a total sexy goddess.
Behati拍照技术超强
Behati takes amazing pictures.
这对模特事业很有帮助
I think it helps, being a model.
她善于捕捉精彩的瞬间
She knows the moments to catch.
她好像总进来偷拍两下
I feel like she just, like, comes in, gets the candid shot.
抱歉啦  姑娘们
Sorry, girls.
Lily热爱音乐
Lily loves music.
她绝对是个摇滚天使
She's definitely owning the rock chick angel right now.
她嫁给一个歌手  并且跟随巡演
To be married to a musician and go on the road
那必须是个音乐狂人
and all those things, you have to love music.
爱音乐才会嫁给音乐人  不是吗
You have to love it to be married to it, right?
Erin真是冰雪聪明
Erin is extremely intelligent.
她什么电子产品都买
She has every gadget you could ever imagine.
我爱极客
她绝对是个性感的电脑迷
She's definitely a sexy nerd.
我喜欢当电脑迷
I love being a nerd.
我最喜欢这样了
I wouldn't want to be any other way.
进入"魔法诱惑"
Going into "Spell on You."
13位女孩们  从摄像头左边开始
13 girls, start camera left.
魔法诱惑
设计"魔法诱惑"这个单元时
In putting together "I Put a Spell on You,"
本系列设计师
我们尝试创造
uh, we were really trying to
朦胧的风情
create the idea of steamy, sultry,
世纪之交的新奥尔良爵士风
turn-of-the-century New Orleans.
这太棒了
This is amazing.
本系列创意总监
开始是纯真的浅色调内衣
It has this innocence of the pale underwear.
有种飘逸仙女的感觉
So you get this floaty, ethereal girl,
但马上转变成黑暗天使
but then rapidly turns into this darker Angel.
非常震撼的造型
It's an amazing look.
这是我最爱的一套
This is my favorite outfit, ever.
为了突出单元特色
To accent this section,
我们主要参考了美国内战前的风格
we relied heavily on Antebellum
混合了法式闺房风格  给人一种
mixed with boudoir, giving kind of a sense of
性感与纯真相结合的感觉
both innocence and sensuality.
[OneRepublic-"Secret"]
放第五首  进入"魔法诱惑"  灯光起
Music track five-- "Spell" and lights!
? I need another story ?
? Something to get off my chest ?
? My life gets kinda boring ?
? Need something that I can confess ?
? Till all my sleeves are stained red ?
? From all the truth that I've said ?
? Come by it honestly, I swear ?
? Thought you saw me wink, no, I've been on the brink, so ?
? Tell me what you want to hear ?
? Something that'll light those ears ?
? I'm sick of all the insincere ?
? So I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
上
Okay, go!
? Don't need another perfect lie ?
? Don't care if critics ever jump in line ?
? I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
? My God ?
? Amazing that we got this far ?
? It's like we're chasing all those stars ?
? Who's driving shiny big black cars ?
? And every day I see the news ?
? All the problems that we could solve ?
? And when a situation rises, just write it into an album ?
? Send it straight to gold ?
? I don't really like my flow, no, so ?
? Tell me what you want to hear ?
? Something that'll light those ears ?
? I'm sick of all the insincere ?
? So I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
? This time ?
? Don't need another perfect lie ?
? Don't care if critics ever jump in line ?
? I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
? Got no reason, got no shame ?
? Got no family I can blame ?
? Just don't let me disappear ?
? I'm-a tell you everything ?
? So tell me what you want to hear ?
? Something that'll light those ears ?
? I'm sick of all the insincere ?
? So I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
? This time ?
? Don't need another perfect lie ?
? Don't care if critics ever jump in line ?
? I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
上吧  Adriana
Go, Adriana!
? So tell me what you want to hear ?
? Something that'll light those ears ?
? Sick of all the insincere ?
? So I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
? This time ?
? Don't need another perfect lie ?
? Don't care if critics ever jump in line ?
? I'm gonna give all my secrets away ?
谢谢
Thank you.
? All my secrets away ?
? And every day I see the news ?
? All the problems that we could solve ?
? And when a situation rises ?
? Just write it into an album ?
? Send it straight to gold ?
? I don't really like my flow, no... ?
Miranda走下天桥了
Miranda's off the runway.
Miranda's clear of the runway.
很好  Nicki Minaj请准备上场
Okay, we're going into Nicki Minaj next.
魔镜魔镜告诉我
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
谁是最美的维密天使
who's the fairest of them all?
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
粉红俱乐部
有请说唱小魔女Nicki Minaj
please welcome the fabulous Nicki Minaj.
? This one is for the boys with the booming system ?
? Top down, AC with the cooling system ?
? When he come up in the club, he be blazin' up ?
? Got stacks on deck like he savin' up ?
? And he ill, he real, he might got a deal ?
? He pop bottles and he got the right kind of bill ?
? He cold, he dope, he might sell, uh ?
? He always in the air but he never fly coach ?
? He a mother lovin' trip, trip, sailor of the ship ?
? When he make it drip, drip, kiss him on the lip, lip ?
? That's the kind of dude I was lookin' for ?
? And yes, you'll get slapped if you're lookin', yo ?
? I said, excuse me, you're a hell of a guy ?
? I mean, m-m-my, my, you're like pelican fly ?
? I mean, you're so shy and I'm loving your tie ?
? You're like slicker than the guy with the thing on his eye ?
? Oh, yes, I did, yes, I did ?
? Somebody please tell him who the hell I is ?
? I am Nicki Minaj, I mack them dudes up ?
? Back coupes up and chuck the deuce up ?
? Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ?
? Beating like a drum and it's coming your way ?
? Can't you hear that ?
? Boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? He got that super bass ?
? Yeah, that's that super bass ?
? Boom, boom, boom, boom ?
? Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, hey ?
? B-b-b-b-b-b-boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? He got that super bass ?
? Boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? Yeah, that's that super bass ?
? This one is for the boys in the polos ?
? Entrepreneur dudes and the moguls ?
? He could ball with the crew, solo ?
? But I think I like him better when he dolo ?
? And I think I like him better with the fitted cap on ?
? He ain't even gotta try to put the MAC on ?
? He just gotta give me that look ?
? When he give me that look ?
? Then the panties comin' off, off, uh ?
? Excuse me, you're a hell of a guy ?
? You know, I really got a thing for American guys ?
? I mean, sigh, sickenin' eyes ?
? I can tell that you're in touch with your feminine side ?
? Oh, yes, I did, yes, I did ?
? Somebody please tell him who the hell I is ?
? I am Nicki Minaj, I mack them dudes up ?
? Back coupes up and chuck the deuce up ?
? Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ?
? Beating like a drum and it's coming your way ?
? Can't you hear that ?
? Boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? He got that super bass ?
? Yeah, that's that super bass ?
? Boom, boom, boom, boom ?
? Boom, boom, boom, bobo ?
? Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom ?
? B-b-b-b-b-b-boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? He got that super bass ?
? Boom, boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? Yeah, that's that super bass ?
? See, I need you in my life for me to stay ?
? No, no, no, no, no, I know you'll stay ?
? No, no, no, no, no ?
? Don't go away, hey, baby ?
? Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ?
? Beating like a drum and it's coming your way ?
? Can't you hear that ?
? Boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ?
? Don't you hear that heartbeat comin' your way ?
? Oh, it be like boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? Yeah. Hey! Hey! ?
? Let's get busy.?
? Come on. Let's go! ?
? Yeah! Whoo! Yeah! ?
? Yeah! Hit it ?
? Boy, you got my heartbeat runnin' away ?
? Beating like a drum and it's coming your way ?
? Can't you hear that ?
? Boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? He got that super bass ?
? Yeah, that's that super bass ?
? B-b-b-b-b-b-boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? He got that super bass ?
? Boom, boom, badoom, boom, boom, badoom, boom, bass ?
? Yeah, that's that super bass ?
? Super bass ?
准备谢幕
Stand by, finale.
谢幕候场
Standing by.
让模特们都上台  请上台
Stagehands now, please. Send the stagehands now.
三  二  一  准备  第七首
Three, two, one. Stand by-- music track seven.
? "There's nothing wrong with loving who you are" ?
? She said, "'Cause he made you perfect, babe" ?
? "So hold your head up, girl, and you'll go far ?
? Listen to me when I say ?
? I'm beautiful in my way 'cause God makes no mistakes ?
? I'm on the right track, baby, I was born this way ?
? Don't hide yourself in regret ?
? Just love yourself and you're set ?
? I'm on the right track, baby ?
? I was born this way, born this way ?
? Oh, there ain't no other way, baby, I was born this way ?
? Baby, I was born this way, born this way ?
? Oh, there ain't no other way ?
? Baby, I was born this way ?
? Right track, baby, I was born this way ?
? Don't be a drag, just be a queen ?
? Na na-na na-na, come on ?
? Come on, come on, come on ?
? 'Cause I may be bad, but I'm perfectly good at it ?
? Sex in the air, I don't care, I love the smell of it ?
? Sticks and stones may break my bones ?
? But chains and whips excite me ?
? Na na na, come on, come on, come on ?
? I like it, like it ?
? Come on, come on ?
? Come on, I like it, like it ?
? Come on, S, S, S and ?
? M, M, M ?
? S, S, S and ?
? S, S, S and M, M, M... ?
再会  明年见
Bye. See you next year.